wemystic.com 2019-03-19

# Privacy Policy - WeMystic

  1. **Identification of the Responsible**

1.1. This Website is property and managed by WeMystic S.A., based on Rua Alfredo Allen, 455 e 461, 4200-135 Porto, Portugal, VAT number 514542934, (“ **WeMystic** “).

1.2. By using this Website, you will be agreeing to the terms described in this privacy policy (“ **Policy** “).

  2. **Personal Data: Collection and Processing**

2.1. Personal data collected and processed by WeMystic are those who you voluntarily put in forms on this Website. However, the filling of these may be necessary to access or obtain certain content or services.

2.2. The personal data collected includes: name, address, telephone, mobile, email, date of birth (or age), gender and, eventually, weight.

2.3. The data are collected through your free, expressed and substantiated consent in a positive act, and the ease with which you make them available is the same as that applicable to the cancellation.

  3. **Personal Data: Purpose of the Processing**

The purpose of the collection and processing of personal data is direct marketing. Your data will only be processed for this determined, explicit and legitimate purpose. The data collected and processed are adequate, relevant and not excessive in relation to this purpose.

  4. **Direct Marketing and Communication of Data to Third Parties**

4.1. By placing a cross and clicking on the “I accept” button (or equivalent) on the forms or chatbots you will consent to receive direct marketing electronic communications. These electronic communications may be effected by email, telephone, mobile phone and SMS/MMS, which the user may choose, at any time, the channel through he or she wishes to be contacted. The communications will be made by WeMystic or by its Partners, also agreeing that WeMystic may transmit its data to its Partners for this purpose.

4.2. WeMystic’s “Partners” are corporate entities, whether public or private, whether or not for profit, and are generally identified at the time of registration or, if not, belong to the category of Esotericism and Spirituality.

4.3. Your personal data may be transferred to third parties when necessary to fulfill legal obligations of WeMystic or a third party subcontractor.

4.4. Your personal data may also be transmitted to subcontracted third parties of WeMystic for the purposes described here, in particular for data storage and transmission of electronic communications services.

  5. **Your Rights**

5.1. To exercise your rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition, forgetting and portability of your personal data can send a written communication to the following email address: “[info@wemystic.com](mailto:info@wemystic.com)“. In this exercise of rights, you must specify the claim, which will be dealt with in a timely manner, within legal deadlines.

5.2. In the specific case of wanting to exercise your right of opposition, stopping to receive marketing communications you can, at all times, exercise it as follows:

  * By clicking on the link for that purpose (usually “unsubscribe” in any email message you receive as a result of your registration on this Website;
  * By sending an email to the address “[info@wemystic.com](mailto:info@wemystic.com)” with the subject “Remove”; or by postal service to the address indicated at the beginning of this privacy policy.

  6. **Security**

WeMystic uses appropriate security measures to protect your personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, changes, unauthorized disclosure or access and against all other unlawful forms of processing. However, as the Internet is not completely secure, you may be warned that the personal data can go through networks without security conditions, with the risk of being seen and used by unauthorized third parties.

  7. **Data Retention**

Your data is stored by WeMystic for the purposes described here, and to prove your registration on this Website, as well as to the exercise of your rights, within the time limits allowable according to the guidelines of the Supervisory entities.

  8. **Other Considerations**

8.1. WeMystic is not responsible for any acts or omissions of third parties, especially with regard to links to other Internet sites and the contents of these.

8.2. In case of merging, division, transformation, dissolution or insolvency of the commercial company WeMystic, your data may be transmitted to third parties as a commercial asset, while always respecting for compliance with the applicable law and keeping your rights while holder of the data, particularly to the consent given and the rights of opposition, access, rectification, unsubscribe, deletion or blocking.

8.3. In case of any legislative or commercial changes, WeMystic reserves the right to change this policy at any time, and should refer to it whenever you use this Website.

8.4. For more information please contact us by email: “[info@wemystic.com](mailto:info@wemystic.com)”

  9. **GDPR Compliance**

9.1. WeMystic is aware of the implementation of the new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), REGULATION (EU) 2016/679 OF THE EUROPEAN PARLIAMENT AND OF THE COUNCIL of 27th of April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data.  
9.2. WeMystic is committed to act in accordance with the regulation, and is taking all steps in this direction.
